What's going on with Xiao Qi?
We're not sure.
He was already here when we arrived today.
Jin Xi, what are you trying to do?
Director,
standing here today,
I actually want to share a new idea with you.
Let's hear it.
What idea?
I think the song "Insect Chirps"
can perfectly reflect
the youthful energy of Ning Caichen.
But I feel just having youthful energy
isn't enough for him.
He has the courage to hold Nie Xiaoqian's hand
and fight against Grandma together.
This shows that deep down,
he is full of wildness and untamed spirit.
Director,
let me show you.
Let's get hyped!
Mr. Heying,
come on.
Come on.
Let's get hyped!
Mr. Heying.
Come on.
Okay, come on.
Okay.
Director,
what do you think?
Jinxi.
Please take Eason outside for a moment.
Okay.
Bro,
you danced so well just now.
It was so hype.
Why do you think the director asked us to come out?
I don't know either.
What's that sound?
It sounds like someone is shouting.
Director,
tell us.
Jinxi,
I don't object
to actors having their own ideas.
But I think your ideas
can be put on hold for now.
Let's continue rehearsing.
Jianshe.
Why do I feel like the director isn't very happy with me?
She is testing you.
She's testing your determination.
If you can persevere,
Jinxi.
Believe me,
you will definitely succeed.
So that's it.
Understood, Jianshe.
Why did the director only scold us
and not Jinxi?
The director only scolds his own people.
If Jinxi keeps this up,
in a few days,
he'll be gone.
Let's go.
The director is single
and lives alone.
But he has a cat named Jinzi.
Named Jinzi.
It even has the same surname as me.
Get to the point.
Does she have anywhere else to go besides home?
Does she have any
hobbies or entertainment activities?
Every morning at 6:00,
she goes to the park to run 10 kilometers on time.
Rain or shine,
she never misses it.
6:00?
Is she even a normal 21st-century human?
I'm curious.
How did you find out about this?
I treated a lot of actors to milk tea.
Bro,
is it really okay for us to track the director's schedule like this?
I have no choice.
Not only in the rehearsal room,
but also in her personal life, I have to tirelessly
pitch my song to her all the time.
Once a challenge starts,
you have to see it through to the end.
Is Jianshe reliable?
Won't doing this make us even more annoying?
You don't understand the director.
She is a very conflicted person.
She's deliberately putting pressure on me
to see if I can stick to my guns
or if it's just a whim.
I hope so.
Nothing.
Left, right, left.
One, two, one.
Morning, Director.
Director.
One, two, one.
What are you doing here?
I just wanted you to listen to my song.
You might like it.
The uncles and aunts all love it.
Right, guys?
Love it.
Stop following me.
Director.
What are you doing?
Director, isn't this song catchy?
Stop singing.
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
I'm sorry.
Can you let people sleep?
Come here.
Why are you making a scene in my hallway?
Director,
you have so many vinyl records here.
I told you before,
it's not that I don't accept your music style.
I have to consider the overall integrity of the play.
I have the exact same set in my studio.
Let me know, in front of the shadow stone.
Let me know, hurried steps.
Jin Xi,
have you been like this since you were a kid?
When you were young,
did you ever go do some
attention-related tests?
What do you mean?
I have told you over and over again
that I don't accept your changes.
Why don't you understand?
I understand.
Understand what?
You are testing me
to see if I can stick to my own creation.
Stick to what?
Brother Jianshe said
we should dare to challenge authority,
even if it's the director.
Once a challenge starts,
you have to see it through to the end.
Director,
you are testing whether I can stick to my creation,
right?
Wait a minute.
Who told you that?
He Ying?
So,
Director,
did I pass the test?
Mr. Heying.
The director said
Jin Xi has been crossing the line lately.
He actually went to her morning run route
to sing his song.
The director was so mad she sent three bomb emojis in a row
and asked if I leaked her whereabouts.
Xiaoqi.
Do you have an idol?
Yes.
Who is it?
Fei Xiang.
Why do you like him?
Because he sings well
and has great style.
Just like...
What if one day
he did something you found despicable,
would you still like him?
No.
My idol must be a person of noble character.
He wouldn't do such a thing.
Fei...
Um, Mr. Heying,
are you okay?
Did I say something wrong?
Heying.
Xiaoqi.
Director,
what brings you here?
I'm looking for Heying.
Are you free later?
I want to have that Chaoshan hot pot again.
Okay, I'll go with you.
Go home early tonight, okay?
Got it.
Director, I want to...
Heying,
I should be the one apologizing to you.
After Jinxi arrived,
I never talked to you about
how you felt about it.
We've worked together on so many shows.
It was my oversight.
I took your understanding nature for granted.
Of course, you have the right to be upset.
In our lives,
there are many unavoidable things.
Some things
I just can't change.
All I can do
is, within my power,
maximize the potential of your character.
I wrote a song for you.
I'll send it to you later.
Director.
Then I need to apologize to you even more.
Heying.
There's someone else you should apologize to.
There are no small parts,
only small actors.
When did I start
becoming the person I hate the most?
Try it, Jianshe.
It smells so good.
Jinxi.
I haven't had this kind of thing in a long time.
You treated me last time.
I must return the favor this time.
Jinxi.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Never mind why.
If I eat this meal,
will you accept my apology?
Eat up.
It's delicious with this fried rice.
Jinxi.
You are still young
and have a fast metabolism.
If I keep eating like this,
I will get fat and old soon.
You will get fat and old even if you don't eat.
It's just a matter of time.
Eat up.
Jinxi.
You are really a special person.
Sister.
Don't worry.
I've been reading palms for years.
You have a great fortune.
Don't worry, Sister.
Nick is very good at this.
You are so rich.
I have money.
But I want some romance.
Okay, Sister, come here.
Boss Wu.
I've been waiting for you.
Let's have a drink together.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Come here.
Have a seat.
Go away.
Sister.
About the copyright of Memories of Jiangnan,
you said it will be adapted into a vertical drama.
Can it make money?
Then how does it make money?
Right.
It relies on click rates.
Then it can make a lot.
Yes.
About our A Chinese Ghost Story,
do you want to know more about it?
I knew it.
You asked me here today
just for this.
Sister, I haven't finished reading your palm yet.
Sister, listen to me first.
No.
Listen to me first.
Let's read the palm first.
I'm reading the palm.
Come closer.
You're not in the frame.
You are truly blessed.
I know.
See if there are any peach blossoms in my palm.
Sister,
look at your peach blossoms.
There are quite a few.
These are all peach blossoms.
How could they be lotuses?
Is that so?
Hello?
What's wrong?
Old Wu.
Unexpected Life.
Do you know about that variety show?
I need to take two days off.
Jin Xi is going to participate in it.
So suddenly?
Didn't I tell you a long time ago?
What's wrong with your memory?
Buy some supplements
to nourish your brain.
Okay.
By the way,
as for the close friend,
pick one from your theater troupe for me.
Close friend?
Anyway, no matter what,
before noon tomorrow,
you must choose someone from your troupe to be the close friend.
Okay.
That's it.
'An Unexpected Life'.
I am especially grateful to the program team
for giving me this opportunity.
Because coming to this farmhouse courtyard
reminds me of many things
from my childhood.
My grandmother's house was similar to this courtyard.
I remember there was a big yellow dog.
It even bit you.
Because we grew up together,
and have been friends since childhood,
so I feel this bond will never change.
You're just putting on an act now.
What do you mean?
How am I putting on an act?
You know it yourself.
Because he has been away for so long
and hasn't contacted us,
we might have drifted apart.
Brother,
you will always be my good brother.
Jinxi
is going to record a variety show,
and wants to find a close friend from our troupe.
After careful consideration...
I think our Heying is the most suitable.
You two look like a good team on stage,
and interact a lot off stage.
Does Jinxi have no friends?
Does she have to find someone from our troupe?
This is a hit S-tier variety show.
If our Heying goes on it,
it will also be great promotion for our troupe.
No.
Both my A and B cast for Ning Caichen are leaving.
How can I rehearse this play without a lead actor?
Why can't you rehearse?
Aren't there still the Black Mountain Demon
and those monsters?
Actually, as the star of Xiyin Troupe,
I don't mind going on a variety show
to promote our troupe.
That's great!
But,
the show Unexpected Life is no good.
This show seems real and simple,
but it is actually pretentious and hypocritical.
The concept it wants to convey is okay.
Stop.
Simply put,
there's no need to say so much.
You just don't want to go.
This young man.
I knew you wouldn't want to go.
Good thing I planned ahead.
Get ready for
Plan B.
I am willing to do it.
Rest assured.
Mr. Wu,
I know this is a very important
promotional opportunity for our troupe.
I will not let you down.
It is a great comfort to have such
a sensible actress in our troupe.
Jin.
Mr. Wu and I have already agreed.
While we are away,
for the roles of Nie Xiaoqian and Ning Caichen,
you and Heying will pair up.
How is that possible?
Why is it impossible?
We are not asking you to perform on stage.
Just partner up for rehearsal for a few days.
The theater troupe isn't just about rehearsing.
Promotion is also a very important job.
A pinch of salt.
Yes, the host Liu Ding.
Can you get an autographed photo for me?
My dad really likes her.
I get it.
Elegant, poised, and intellectual types like her.
Don't worry.
I'll ask for it as soon as I see her.
No problem.
You're so sweet.
Come and eat.
Jinxi.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Come have some dessert.
Dessert?
Jealous?
This is an exclusive perk of the Xiyin Troupe.
They're low-calorie, low-sugar cakes specially made by Ning Jin.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
You made all these?
She made them all.
Do you know who's sitting in front of you?
She is Xiyin Troupe's top chef, Ning Jin.
These desserts are just the tip of the iceberg.
Her cooking is the real deal.
She's mastered all eight culinary traditions.
The craziest part is
that she can single-handedly
cook 14 or 15 dishes for the whole troupe.
Flavors from all over the country are a piece of cake for her.
A piece of cake.
That's only because
not a single one of you can be my sous-chef.
That's because you are too picky.
You think
none of us can do anything right.
You kick us out over the slightest mistake.
Putting cooking wine in the pot instead of soy sauce
is not a small mistake.
Exactly.
Eating too much of it will kill you.
People could die.
Director.
Boss Wu is looking for you and Jinxi.
Why can't our Bai Feixin do it?
Bai Feixin has ulterior motives towards our Jinxi.
He's always trying to piggyback off her.
There are rumors about the two of them all over the internet right now.
If they go together,
won't that just add fuel to the fire?
We're all adults here.
Hyping them up as a couple won't kill anyone.
Don't you know Jinxi's positioning?
I don't know.
Hype my foot!
That sounds like a dish name.
Just watch your video.
Director,
why don't you go?
Let that Xiao Ba from your troupe lead the rehearsal.
That minimizes the impact, doesn't it?
I'm not going.
As long as you go,
I can talk to the show's crew
to schedule the broadcast
before your tour.
It can also boost your box office.
It's the same promotion.
What's the difference between me going and Bai Feixin going?
Of course it's different.
Your musical qualifications are much better than hers.
Besides, if she goes with Jinxi,
will anyone still focus on your work?
It'll be nothing but gossip.
Then if I go alone with the director,
there won't be any gossip, right?
So it's settled.
I've unilaterally decided
to let Bai Feixin and Director Ning go together.
We can consider it.
Are you kidding me?
The production crew didn't say the best friend has to be just one person.
I'm not going.
Ning Jin.
Do me a favor.
I'm begging you.
Fine.
What's the worst that could happen?
A small theater troupe,
with no promotional budget.
At worst, during performances,
the box office fails,
and the troupe disbands.
I will
sell everything I own
to give these kids some severance pay.
But...
but these...
these young people...
their musical theater journey...
their path of pursuing art...
I'll go just this once.
It's a deal.
What about Bai Feixin?
I'm still willing.
What do you want now?
Director,
let me come in first.
No.
Tell me first,
why did you come over without giving me a heads-up?
Can you let me...
let me in first?
No.
I brought milk tea.
Who allowed you to just show up at my house for no reason?
I really have an emergency, Director.
Please help me out.
Come in.
Thank you, Director.
Cooking?
Previously in 'Unexpected Life',
there was a cooking segment.
One guest said
he was very good at cooking.
But no one ate what he made,
and he was mocked online for a long time.
Then why didn't you just tell them
that you can't cook?
The point is, I can.
What can you make?
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
What else?
Do instant noodles count?
No.
Then that's it.
Then you don't know how to cook at all.
So please help me, Director.
I can't go on the show
and make a table full of instant noodles
and scrambled eggs with tomatoes for everyone.
Okay, come with me.
Let's prepare the ingredients first,
scallion and ginger.
Then look.
Make sure your hands are like this.
Like this?
Yes, press it with your nails.
You give it a try.
Hand.
Hook it like this.
Right?
Right.
Are you okay?
Just kidding.
Learn it well.
You have to add it now.
Otherwise, it won't taste good.
Director,
try it.
How is it?
Not bad.
I told you.
I've made this dish before.
Come try this.
It's my first time making shredded potatoes.
How is it?
It's a bit sour.
I put too much vinegar.
Did you order takeout?
Open the door.
Who is it?
It's me,
Bai Feixin.
Why is she here?
Go hide inside quickly.
Hurry.
Where is she?
Feixin.
Ma has fallen for Zhiwei.
Wait a minute.
Who is Ma?
Ma,
the newcomer to the group.
The one with the big eyes,
who played the innkeeper.
Are you close to her?
That's not important now.
What's important is Zhiwei.
He has someone he likes,
and that person is Qianying.
But I can't tell Xiaoma,
because I promised Zhiwei to keep it a secret.
Don't you think it's hard for me?
What's the relationship between Zhiwei and Qianying
now?
That's a
long story.
I'll tell you all about it in detail tonight
when we're in bed.
You made so many dishes.
I can help you eat some.
Ning Jin.
You've worked hard.
I know
you usually eat alone at home
and feel lonely.
But instead of setting an extra set of tableware,
why don't you find a real partner?
Who said they're empty?
I'm hiding a man in my house right now.
He's right in my bedroom.
You'll see him if you open the door, believe it or not.
I haven't heard anything this funny in a long time.
Eat.